Guide to the Vassar College Photograph Files, approximately 1865-2014
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901. Individuals. L-S (Folder 12.24)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901. Individuals. T-Z, unidentified (Folder 12.25)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901. Small groups (Folder 12.25)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901. Group Compilation (OV3.134)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1902. Individuals. A-H (Folder 13.1)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1902. Individuals. K-R (Folder 13.2)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1902. Individuals. S-Z (Folder 13.3)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1903 (OV1.140)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1903 (OV2.062)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1903 (OV3.074)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1903. Individuals (OV1.141)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1903. Individuals. A-K (Folder 13.4)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1903. Individuals. L-Z (Folder 13.5)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1904 (OV2.063)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1904 (OV3.073)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1904 (OV3.075-OV3.077)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1904. Individuals. A-H (Folder 13.6)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1904. Individuals. J-U (Folder 13.7)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1904. Individuals. V-Z (Folder 13.7A)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1904. Small groups (Folder 13.7A)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1905 (OV2.064)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1905 (OV3.033-OV3.035)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1905 (OV3.078-OV3.080)
- V. C. Students. Class of [1905?] (OV3.083)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1905. Group Compilation (OV3.135)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1905. Individuals (Folder 13.8)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1906 (OV1.142)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1906 (OV3.036-OV3.038)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1906. Individuals (Folder 13.9)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1906. Small groups (Folder 13.9)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1907 (OV2.065)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1907 (OV3.039)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1907. Individuals (Folder 13.10)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1908 (OV2.066)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1908 (OV3.040)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1908. Individuals (Folder 13.11)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1908. Small groups (Folder 13.11)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1908. Mary Taylor (OV1.143)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1909 (OV1.144)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1909 (OV2.067)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1909. Individuals (Folder 13.12)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1909. Small groups (Folder 13.12)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1910 (OV2.068)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1910. Individuals (Folder 13.13)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1910. Small groups (Folder 13.13)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1911 (OV1.145)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1911 (OV2.069)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1911 (OV3.041)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1911. Individuals. A-H (Folder 13.14)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1911. Individuals. J-Z (Folder 13.15)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1911. Small groups (Folder 13.15)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1912 (OV1.146)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1912 (OV2.070)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1912. Individuals. (Folder 13.16)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1912. Small groups (Folder 13.16)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1913 (OV1.147)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1913 (OV2.071)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1913. Individuals (Folder 13.17)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1913. Small groups (Folder 13.17)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1913. Lucy Penniman (OV1.148)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1914 (OV2.072)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1914 (OV3.042-OV3.043)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1914. Individuals (Folder 13.18)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1914. Small groups (Folder 13.18)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1915 (OV1.149)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1915 (OV2.073)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1915. Individuals (Folder 13.19)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1915. Small groups (Folder 13.19)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1915. Martha Reynolds (OV1.150)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1916 (OV1.151)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1916 (OV2.074)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1916. Individuals (Folder 13.20)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1917 (OV2.075)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1917-1918. Individuals (Folder 13.21)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1918 (OV1.152)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1918 (OV2.076)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1918 (OV3.044)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1918. Small groups (Folder 13.21)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1918. Lucille Phillips (OV2.077)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1919 (OV1.153)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1919 (OV2.078)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1919-1920. Individuals (Folder 13.22)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1920 (OV1.154)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1920 (OV2.079)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1920. Barbara Romcyn (OV1.155)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1921 (OV1.156)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1921 (OV3.045)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1921-1922. Individuals (Folder 13.23)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1922 (OV1.157)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1922 (OV2.080)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1922. Jean Ford (OV1.158)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1922. Louise Holcombe (OV1.159)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1923 (OV1.160)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1923 (OV2.081)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1923 (OV3.017)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1923. Elizabeth Merrill (OV1.161)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1923-1924. Individuals (Folder 13.24)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1924 (OV2.082)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1924 (OV3.018)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1925 (OV1.162)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1925 (OV2.083)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1925 (OV3.098)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1925. Individuals (Folder 13.25A)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1926. Individuals (Folder 13.25B)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1926 (OV2.084)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1926 (OV3.019)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1926 (OV3.099-OV3.100)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1925. Small groups (Folder 13.25)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1926. Small groups (Folder 13.25)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1927 (OV2.085)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1927 (OV3.101-OV3.102)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1927. Margaret Fisher (OV1.163)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1927. Margaret Fisher (OV2.086)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1927. Small groups (Folder 13.26)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1927-1929. Individuals (Folder 13.26)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1928 (OV1.164)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1928 (OV2.087)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1928 (OV3.046-OV3.047)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1928 (OV3.103)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1928. Small groups (Folder 13.26)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1929 (OV1.165)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1929 (OV2.088)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1930 (OV2.089)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1930. Margaret Pulsifer (OV1.166)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1930-1934. Individuals (Folder 13.27)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1931 (OV1.216)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1932 (OV1.167)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1932 (OV2.090)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1933 (OV1.168)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1933 (OV3.048)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1933. Individuals (Folders 13.28-13.31)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1935 (OV2.091)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1935. Group: Freshman and/or Senior Year Photos (Folder 13.33)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1935-1938. Individuals (Folder 13.32)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1936 (OV2.092)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1937 (OV2.093)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1937. Florence Hardy (OV1.169)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1938 (OV1.170)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1938 (OV2.094)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1939 (OV2.095)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1939. Small groups (Folder 13.34)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1940 (OV3.049)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1940-1943. Individuals (Folder 13.35)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1940-1943. Small groups (Folder 13.35)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1941 (OV1.171)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1941 (OV2.096)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1942 (OV2.097)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1942. Individuals (Folder 13.36)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1943 (OV1.172)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1943 (OV2.098)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1943 (OV3.050)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1944 (OV1.173)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1944 (OV2.099)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1945 (OV1.174)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1945 (OV3.051)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1944-1945. Individuals (Folder 13.37)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1944-1945. Small groups (Folder 13.37)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1946 (OV1.175)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1946 (OV2.100)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1946-48. Individuals (Folder 13.38)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1950. Individuals (Folder 13.39)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1954. Individuals (Folder 13.40)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1955. Candy Smith (OV1.176)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1956. Individuals (Folder 13.41)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1957. Individuals (Folder 13.42)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1958. Individuals (Folder 13.43)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1959. Individuals (Folder 13.44)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1960. Individuals (Folder 13.45)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1961-1969. Individuals (Folder 13.46)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1961-1969. Individuals (OV1.177)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1970-1979. Individuals (Folder 13.47a)
- V. C. Students. Classes of 1980-1990. Individuals (Folder 13.47b)
- V. C. Students. Class of 2006. Freshman Year Group, 2002 (Folder OV3.138)
- V. C. Students. Class of 2007. Freshman Year Group, 2003 (Folder OV3.139)
- V. C. Students. Class of 2009. Freshman Year Group, 2005; [2 copies] (Folder OV3.140)
- V. C. Students. Class of 2010. Freshman Year Group, 2006; [2 copies] (Folder OV3.141)
- V. C. Students. Class of 2018. Freshman Year Group, 2014; [2 copies] (Folder OV3.147)
- V. C. Students. Individuals. Unidentified (OV3.056-OV3.057)
- V. C. Students. Individuals. Unidentified (OV3.060)
- V. C. Students. Class Officers, Student Government. House Officers, 1895-1949, undated (Folder 13.48)
- V. C. Students. Class Officers, Student Government. House Officers, 1950-1954 (Folder 13.49)
- V. C. Students. Class Officers, Student Government. House Officers, 1954-1970 (Folder 13.50)
- V. C. Students. Clubs, 1895-1949, undated (Folder 13.51)
- V. C. Students. Clubs, 1950-1954 (Folder 13.52)
- V. C. Students. Clubs, 1955-1969 (Folder 13.53)
- V. C. Students. Cooperative Housekeeping, undated (Folder 13.54)
- V. C. Students. Cooperative Housekeeping, 1936-1971 (Folder 13.55)
- V. C. Students. Costumes, undated (Folder 13.56)
- V. C. Students. Costumes, 1867-1929 (Folder 13.57)
- V. C. Students. Costumes, 1930-1985 (Folder 13.58)
- V. C. Students. Daisy-picking (Folder 13.59)
- V. C. Students. Daisy-picking (OV1.178)
- V. C. Students. Daisy-picking (OV3.092)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Unidentified (Folders 14.1-14.4)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Miscellaneous, 1939 (Folder 14.5)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Miscellaneous, 1940-1949 (Folder 14.6)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Miscellaneous, 1950-1959 (Folders 14.7-14.8)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Miscellaneous, 1960-1969 (Folder 14.9)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Miscellaneous, 1970-1989 (Folder 14.10)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Freshman Dance (Folder 14.11)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Sophomore Hop (Folder 14.12)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Junior Proms, 1930-1947 (Folder 14.13)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Junior Proms, 1933 (OV3.054)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Junior Proms, 1941 (OV3.052-OV3.053)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Junior Proms, 1948-1949 (Folder 14.14)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Junior Proms, 1950-1969 (Folder 14.15)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Junior Proms (OV1.179)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Junior Proms (OV2.101)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Junior Proms (OV2.106)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1916, 1920 (OV2.102)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1919 (OV1.180)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1926 (OV1.182)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1930-1935 (OV1.181)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1930-1935 (OV2.102)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1938-1939 (Folder 14.16)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1940-1949 (Folder 14.17)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1940-1949 (OV2.104)
- V. C. Students. Dances. Senior Proms, 1950- (Folder 14.18)
- V. C. Students. Debating (Folder 14.19)
- V. C. Students. Debating (OV1.183)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, undated (OV1.184)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, undated (OV2.105)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics. Japanese 'Hauta' Dancing, undated (OV3.097)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1870-1879 (Folder 14.20)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1880-1889 (Folders 14.21-14.22)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, circa 1880-1899, undated (Folder 14.27)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1890-1899 (Folders 14.23-14.24)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics. Antigone, 1893 (Folders 14.25-14.26)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1900-1907 (Folder 14.28)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, circa 1900-1910, undated (Folder 14.31)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1908 (Folder 14.29)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1909-1910 (Folder 14.30)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, circa 1910-1919, undated (Folder 14.40-14.41)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1911-1912 (Folder 14.32)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1913 (Folder 14.33)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1914-1915 (Folder 14.34)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics. Pageant of Athena, 1915 (Folder 14.35)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1916-1917 (Folder 14.36)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1918 (Folder 14.37)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1919 (Folder 14.38-14.39)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, circa 1920-1929, undated (Folder 14.50-14.51)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1920 (Folder 14.42-14.43)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1921 (Folder 14.44)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1922 (Folder 14.45)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1923 (Folder 14.46)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics. Kenilworth Revels, 1924 (Folder 14.48)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1924-1925 (Folder 14.47)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. Deirdre of the Sorrows, 1925 (OV3.094)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1926-1929 (Folder 14.49)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. The Urfaust, 1927 (OV3.094)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. Lorenzo the Magnificent, 1928 (OV3.095)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. George Barnwell, 1930 (Folder 14.52)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. Monsieur Beaucaire, 1930 (OV3.095)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1930-1935 (Folder 15.1)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. The Tempest, 1931 (OV3.095)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. The Knight's Tale, Noah, and The Sad Shepherd, 1932-1935 (OV3.126)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. The Swan, 1933 (OV3.094)
- V.C. Students. Dramatics. The Green Cockatoo, Bedrock, and The Vest Pocket Standby, 1934-1935 (OV3.127)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1936-1937 (Folder 15.2)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics. Spring Dance, The Learned Ladies, and Liluli, 1938-1939 (OV3.117)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1938 (Folder 15.3)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1939 (Folder 15.4)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1940 (Folder 15.5)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics. The Yellow Jacket, 1940 (OV3.096)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics. Stage Door, 1940 (OV3.116)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, circa 1940-1949 (Folder 15.9)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1941 (Folder 15.6)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1942-1946 (Folder 15.7)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1947-1949 (Folder 15.8)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1950-1959 (Folder 15.10)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, circa 1950-1959, undated (Folder 15.11)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1960-1969 (Folder 15.12)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, 1970- (Folder 15.13)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, undated (OV1.184)
- V. C. Students. Dramatics, undated (OV2.105)
- [EMPTY] (Folder 15.14)
- V. C. Students. Eating and Eating Clubs (Folder 15.15)
- V. C. Students. Foreign Students, 1920-1949, undated (Folder 15.16)
- V. C. Students. Foreign Students, 1950- (Folder 15.17)
- V. C. Students. Foreign Students, undated (OV1.185)
- V. C. Students. Freshman Registration & Orientation (Folder 15.18)
- V. C. Students. "Granddaughters" (daughters & granddaughters of alumnae) (Folder 15.19)
- V. C. Students. Students. Health Services (Folder 15.20)
- V. C. Students. Horizons Unlimited (Folder 15.21)
- V. C. Students. Horseback Riding (Folder 15.22)
- V. C. Students. Junior Party, 1895-1920 (Folder 15.23)
- V. C. Students. Junior Party, 1921-1929 (Folder 15.24)
- V. C. Students. Junior Party, 1930-1956, undated (Folder 15.24a)
- V. C. Students. Mandolin Club (Folder 15.25)
- V. C. Students. Mandolin Club (OV2.107)
- V. C. Students. Mandolin Club (OV2.108)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1860-1869 (Folder 15.26)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1867 (OV3.129)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1870-1879 (Folder 15.27)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1870-1879 (Odd formats box)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1880-1889 (Folder 15.28)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1890-1895 (Folder 15.29)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1896-1899 (Folder 15.30)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1900-1904 (Folder 15.31)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1900-1904 (OV1.186)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1900-1904 (OV2.109)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1900-1904 (OV2.110)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1900-1904 (OV3.032)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1905-1909 (Folder 15.32)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1910-1914 (Folder 15.33)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1915-1919 (Folder 15.34)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1920-1929, undated (Folder 15.35)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1920-1930 (Folder 15.36)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1931-[1950?], undated (OV3.031)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1931-1940 (Folder 15.37)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1940-1949, undated (Folder 15.38)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1941-1944 (Folder 15.39)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1949 (OV3.016)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1945-1950 (Folder 15.40)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1940-1959, undated (OV3.020)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1940-1959, undated (Folder 15.41)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1950-1959, undated (OV1.187)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1950-1959, undated (OV2.111)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1950-1959, undated (OV3.064)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1951-1953 (Folder 15.42)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1954-1959 (Folder 16.1)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1950-1959 (Folder 16.2)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1960-1969, undated (Folder 16.3)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups, 1960-1969 (Folder 16.4)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups. 1970 - (Folder 16.5)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups. 1970 - (OV3.108)
- V. C. Students. Miscellaneous Groups. 1970 - (OV3.111-OV3.114)
- V. C. Students. Moving Day (Folder 16.6)
- V. C. Students. Music Piano Playing (OV3.057)
- V. C. Students. Orchestra & Chamber Music, etc. (Folder 16.7)
- V. C. Students. Orchestra & Chamber Music, etc. (OV2.112)
- V. C. Students. Outdoor Activities (Folder 16.8)
- V. C. Students. Painting (OV3.015)
- V. C. Students. Parties and Holidays (Folder 16.9)
- V. C. Students. Periodicals (including editorial boards), undated (Folder 16.10)
- V. C. Students. Periodicals (including editorial boards). 1895 - (Folder 16.11)
- V. C. Students. Political Activities, [?]-1940 (Folder 16.12)
- V. C. Students. Political Activities, 1950-1959 (Folder 16.13)
- V. C. Students. Political Activities. 1960 - (Folder 16.14)
- V. C. Students. Radio Workshop & Radio Station, & TV (Folder 16.15)
- V. C. Students. Scholarships, Fellowships, Awards, etc. (Folder 16.16)
- V. C. Students. Self-help Activities (Folder 16.17)
- V. C. Students. Senior Circus (Folder 16.18)
- V. C. Students. Senior Howl, 1899 (Folder 16.19)
- V. C. Students. Singing. General (Folder 16.20)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. Choir, undated (Folder 16.21)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. Choir, 1928-1969 (Folder 16.22)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. Floradoras (Folder 16.23)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. G. Stringers (Folder 16.24)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. Glee Club (Folder 16.25)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. Gold Dusters (Folder 16.26)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. Madrigals (Folder 16.27)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. Miscellaneous (Folder 16.28)
- V. C. Students. Singing Groups. Night Owls (Folder 16.29)
- V. C. Students. Skating (Folder 16.30)
- V. C. Students. Skating (OV3.055)
- V. C. Students. Skeptics' Corner (Folder 16.31)
- V. C. Students. Smoking (Folder 16.32)
- V. C. Students. Smoking (OV3.058)
- V. C. Students. Sophomore Party, take offs, etc., 1911-1922 (Folder 16.33)
- V. C. Students. Sophomore Party, take offs, etc., 1923-1950 (Folder 16.34)
- V. C. Students. Sophomore Party, take offs, etc., 1951-1962, undated (Folder 16.35)
- V. C. Students. Students' Association & College Government Association (Folder 16.36)
- V. C. Students. Students' Association & College Government Association (OV2.113)
- V. C. Students. Studying (Folder 16.37)
- V. C. Students. Studying, circa 1950s (OV3.142-OV3.144)
- V. C. Students. Suffrage Parade & Activities (Folder 16.38)
- V. C. Students. Summer Jobs and Activities, 1987-1955, undated (Folder 16.39)
- V. C. Students. Summer Jobs and Activities, 1956 (Folder 16.40)
- V. C. Students. Summer Jobs and Activities. 1957 - (Folder 16.41)
- V. C. Students. Sunbathing (Folder 16.42)
- V. C. Students. Tree Day, [?]-1916 (Folder 16.43)
- V. C. Students. Tree Day, 1917-1939 (Folder 16.44)
- V. C. Students. Tree Day. 1940 - (Folder 16.45)
- V. C. Students. Trig Ceremonies (Folder 16.46)
- V. C. Students. TV/Radio Appearances (Folder 16.47)
- V. C. Students. Volunteer Activities (Folder 16.48)
- V. C. Students. Weekend Activities. undated (Folder 16.49)
- V. C. Students. Weekend Activities, [?]-1967 (Folder 16.50)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Adults, 1940-1949, undated (Folder 16.51)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Adults, 1940-1949, undated (OV1.188)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Adults, 1950-1969 (Folder 16.52)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Adults, 1964 (OV3.028)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Children, undated (Folder 17.1)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Children, undated (OV1.189-OV1.190)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Children, undated (OV2.114)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Children, 1930-1939 (Folder 17.3)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Children, 1940-1949 (Folder 17.4)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Children, 1950-1956 (Folder 17.5)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Children, 1957 (Folder 17.6)
- V. C. Summer Institute. Children, 1958 (Folder 17.7)
- V. C. Swupper Club (Folder 17.8)
- V. C. Township Day & Community Day (Folder 17.9)
- V. C. Trustees, Board of (Folder 17.10)
- V. C. Trustees, Board of, 2011 (OV3.146)
- V. C. Urban Center for Black Studies (Folder 17.11)
- V. C. Vassar Players (Folder 17.12)
- V. C. Veterans (Folder 17.13)
- V. C. Views. Arboretum, etc. (Folder 17.14)
- V. C. Views. Bicycles (Folders 17.15-17.16)
- V. C. Views. Bicycles (OV1.191)
- V. C. Views. Circle (Folder 17.17)
- V. C. Views. Circle (OV1.191)
- V. C. Views. V. C. Faculty Gardens (Folder 17.18)
- V. C. Views. V. C. Faculty Houses (Folder 17.19)
- V. C. Views. V. C. Faculty Row (Folder 17.20)
- V. C. Views. V. C. Faculty Row (OV1.193)
- V. C. Views. Farm (Folder 17.21)
- V. C. Views. Farm (OV1.194)
- V. C. Views. Gardens. etc. (Folder 17.22)
- V. C. Views. Gates. etc. (Folder 17.23)
- V. C. Views. Gates. etc. (OV1.195)
- V. C. Views. General. dated (Folder 17.24)
- V. C. Views. General, 1865 (OV2.115)
- V. C. Views. General, 1907 (OV3.061)
- V. C. Views. General, undated (Folders 17.25-17.28)
- V. C. Views. General, undated (OV1.196)
- V. C. Views. General, undated (OV2.121)
- V. C. Views. General. Aerial (Folder 17.29)
- V. C. Views. General. Aerial (OV1.197)
- V. C. Views. General. Aerial (OV3.063)
- V. C. Views. General. Aerial (OV3.128)
- V. C. Views. General Blueprints, circa 1894 (Folder 17.30)
- V. C. Views. General. Indelible photographs, circa 1890 (Folder 17.31)
- V. C. Views. Golf Course (Folder 17.32)
- V. C. Views. Golf Course (OV3.062)